1. file = new java.io.FileInputStream(new java.io.File((java.lang.System.getProperty(user.dir) + \Data Files\dataFile.xlsx)))
5. workbook = new org.apache.poi.xssf.usermodel.XSSFWorkbook(file)
9. sheet = workbook.getSheetAt(0)
15. Launch browser
21. Navigate to url http://automationexercise.com
27. Verify that home page is visible successfully
31. verifyElementAttributeValue(findTestObject("Object Repository/Login/Menu_Home"), "style", "color: orange;", Short_Timeout)
35. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Object Repository/Login/img_Home"), OPTIONAL)
41. Click on "Signup / Login" button
47. Verify "Login to your account" is visible
53. Enter correct email address
59. Enter correct email address
65. Click on "Login" button
71. Verify logged in user