1. file = new java.io.FileInputStream(new java.io.File((java.lang.System.getProperty(user.dir) + \Data Files\dataFile.xlsx)))
5. workbook = new org.apache.poi.xssf.usermodel.XSSFWorkbook(file)
9. sheet = workbook.getSheetAt(0)
15. Launch browser
19. maximizeWindow()
25. Navigate to url http://automationexercise.com
31. Verify that home page is visible successfully
35. verifyElementAttributeValue(findTestObject("Object Repository/Login/Menu_Home"), "style", "color: orange;", Short_Timeout)
39. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Object Repository/Login/img_Home"), OPTIONAL)
45. Click on "Signup / Login" button
51. Verify "New User Signup!" is visible
57. Enter "Name"
63. Enter "Email" Address
67. myDateObj = LocalDateTime.now()
71. out.println("Before formatting: " + myDateObj)
75. myFormatObj = DateTimeFormatter.ofPattern("ddMMyyyy")
79. formattedDate = myDateObj.format(myFormatObj)
83. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Login/txt_Email"), "Test" + formattedDate + "@" + random + ".com")
89. Write data to excel for email
95. Click "Signup" button
101. Verify that "ENTER ACCOUNT INFORMATION" is visible
105. verifyElementAttributeValue(findTestObject("Object Repository/Account Info/verify_Email"), "value", "Test" + formattedDate + "@" + random + ".com", Short_Timeout)
111. Select the "Title"
117. Set the "Password" for our logged in user
123. Write data to excel for email
129. Set The Date of Birth
133. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Object Repository/Account Info/drp_Month"), Short_Timeout)
137. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("Object Repository/Account Info/drp_Month"), "3", false)
141. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("Object Repository/Account Info/drp_Year"), "2002", false)
147. Select checkbox "Sign up for our newsletter!"
151. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Account Info/checkbox_signUpNews"))
157. Select checkbox "Receive special offers from our partners!"
163. Enter "First name"
167. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Account Info/txt_first_name"), "KBC")
173. Enter "Last name"
179. Enter "Company"
185. Enter "Address"
191. Enter "Address 2"
197. Select "Country"
203. Enter "State"
207. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Account Info/txt_State"), "ACT")
213. Enter "City"
219. Enter "ZipCode"
225. Enter "ZipCode"
231. Click "Create Account button"
235. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Account Info/btn_CreateAcc"))
241. Verify that "ACCOUNT CREATED!" is visible
247. Click "Continue" button
253. Verify that "Logged in as username" is visible
257. file.close()
261. outFile = new java.io.FileOutputStream(new java.io.File((java.lang.System.getProperty(user.dir) + \Data Files\dataFile.xlsx)))
265. workbook.write(outFile)
269. outFile.close()
273. closeBrowser()