1. file = new java.io.FileInputStream(new java.io.File((java.lang.System.getProperty(user.dir) + \Data Files\dataFile.xlsx)))
5. workbook = new org.apache.poi.xssf.usermodel.XSSFWorkbook(file)
9. sheet = workbook.getSheetAt(0)
15. Read data from excel
19. password = getCell(1).getStringCellValue()
25. Call Login test case to run the login test
3. Open Browser
9. Navigate to url http://automationexercise.com
15. Verify that home page is visible successfully
19. verifyElementAttributeValue(findTestObject("Object Repository/Login/Menu_Home"), "style", "color: orange;", Short_Timeout)
23. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Object Repository/Login/img_Home"), OPTIONAL)
29. Click on "Signup / Login" button
35. Verify "Login to your account" is visible
41. Enter correct email address
47. Enter correct email address
53. Click on "Login" button
59. Verify logged in user
29. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Login/btn_Logout"))
33. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Object Repository/Login/img_Home"), OPTIONAL)