1. file = new java.io.FileInputStream(new java.io.File((java.lang.System.getProperty(user.dir) + \Data Files\dataFile.xlsx)))
5. workbook = new org.apache.poi.xssf.usermodel.XSSFWorkbook(file)
9. sheet = workbook.getSheetAt(0)
15. Launch browser
21. Navigate to url http://automationexercise.com
27. Verify that home page is visible successfully
31. verifyElementAttributeValue(findTestObject("Object Repository/Login/Menu_Home"), "style", "color: orange;", Short_Timeout)
35. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Object Repository/Login/img_Home"), OPTIONAL)
41. Click on "Signup / Login" button
47. Verify "New User Signup!" is visible
53. Enter "Name"
59. Enter "Email" Address
63. myDateObj = LocalDateTime.now()
67. out.println("Before formatting: " + myDateObj)
71. myFormatObj = DateTimeFormatter.ofPattern("ddMMyyyy")
75. formattedDate = myDateObj.format(myFormatObj)
79. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Login/txt_Email"), "Test" + formattedDate + "@" + random + ".com")
85. Write data to excel for email
91. Click "Signup" button
97. Verify that "ENTER ACCOUNT INFORMATION" is visible
101. verifyElementAttributeValue(findTestObject("Object Repository/Account Info/verify_Email"), "value", "Test" + formattedDate + "@" + random + ".com", Short_Timeout)
107. Select the "Title"
113. Set the "Password" for our logged in user
119. Write data to excel for email
125. Set The Date of Birth
129. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Object Repository/Account Info/drp_Month"), Short_Timeout)
133. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("Object Repository/Account Info/drp_Month"), "3", false)
137. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("Object Repository/Account Info/drp_Year"), "2002", false)
143. Select checkbox "Sign up for our newsletter!"
147. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Account Info/checkbox_signUpNews"))
153. Select checkbox "Receive special offers from our partners!"
159. Enter "First name"
163. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Account Info/txt_first_name"), "KBC")
169. Enter "Last name"
175. Enter "Company"
181. Enter "Address"
187. Enter "Address 2"
193. Select "Country"
199. Enter "State"
203. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Account Info/txt_State"), "ACT")
209. Enter "City"
215. Enter "ZipCode"
221. Enter "ZipCode"
227. Click "Create Account button"
231. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Account Info/btn_CreateAcc"))
237. Verify that "ACCOUNT CREATED!" is visible
243. Click "Continue" button
249. Verify that "Logged in as username" is visible
253. file.close()
257. outFile = new java.io.FileOutputStream(new java.io.File((java.lang.System.getProperty(user.dir) + \Data Files\dataFile.xlsx)))
261. workbook.write(outFile)
265. outFile.close()