1. file = new java.io.FileInputStream(new java.io.File((java.lang.System.getProperty(user.dir) + \Data Files\dataFile.xlsx)))
5. workbook = new org.apache.poi.xssf.usermodel.XSSFWorkbook(file)
9. sheet = workbook.getSheetAt(0)
15. Read data from excel
19. password = getCell(1).getStringCellValue()
23. callTestCase(findTestCase("Login/L002_Login User with correct email and password"), ["userEmail":userEmail, "password":password], STOP_ON_FAILURE)
1. file = new java.io.FileInputStream(new java.io.File((java.lang.System.getProperty(user.dir) + \Data Files\dataFile.xlsx)))
5. workbook = new org.apache.poi.xssf.usermodel.XSSFWorkbook(file)
9. sheet = workbook.getSheetAt(0)
15. Read data from excel
19. password = getCell(1).getStringCellValue()
25. Launch browser
31. Navigate to url http://automationexercise.com
37. Verify that home page is visible successfully
41. verifyElementAttributeValue(findTestObject("Object Repository/Login/Menu_Home"), "style", "color: orange;", Short_Timeout)
45. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Object Repository/Login/img_Home"), OPTIONAL)
51. Click on "Signup / Login" button
57. Verify "Login to your account" is visible
63. Enter correct email address
69. Enter correct email address
75. Click on "Login" button
81. Verify logged in user
87. Click "Delete Account" button
93. Verify that "ACCOUNT DELETED!" is visible and click "Continue" button
99. Click "Continue" button
103. closeBrowser()