1. file = new java.io.FileInputStream(new java.io.File((java.lang.System.getProperty(user.dir) + \Data Files\dataFile.xlsx)))
5. workbook = new org.apache.poi.xssf.usermodel.XSSFWorkbook(file)
9. sheet = workbook.getSheetAt(0)
15. Read data from excel
19. password = getCell(1).getStringCellValue()
25. Call Login test case to run the login test
1. file = new java.io.FileInputStream(new java.io.File((java.lang.System.getProperty(user.dir) + \Data Files\dataFile.xlsx)))
5. workbook = new org.apache.poi.xssf.usermodel.XSSFWorkbook(file)
9. sheet = workbook.getSheetAt(0)
15. Read data from excel
19. password = getCell(1).getStringCellValue()
23. UserEmail = userEmail
27. Password = password
31. openBrowser("")
37. Navigate to url http://automationexercise.com
43. Verify that home page is visible successfully
47. verifyElementAttributeValue(findTestObject("Object Repository/Login/Menu_Home"), "style", "color: orange;", Short_Timeout)
51. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Object Repository/Login/img_Home"), OPTIONAL)
57. Click on "Signup / Login" button
63. Verify "Login to your account" is visible
69. Enter correct email address
75. Enter correct email address
81. Click on "Login" button
87. Verify logged in user
91. closeBrowser()
31. Verify logged in user