1. file = new java.io.FileInputStream(new java.io.File((java.lang.System.getProperty(user.dir) + \Data Files\dataFile.xlsx)))
5. workbook = new org.apache.poi.xssf.usermodel.XSSFWorkbook(file)
9. sheet = workbook.getSheetAt(0)
15. Read data from excel
19. password = getCell(1).getStringCellValue()
23. UserEmail = userEmail
27. Password = password
33. Launch browser
39. Navigate to url http://automationexercise.com
45. Verify that home page is visible successfully
49. verifyElementAttributeValue(findTestObject("Object Repository/Login/Menu_Home"), "style", "color: orange;", Short_Timeout)
53. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Object Repository/Login/img_Home"), OPTIONAL)
59. Click on "Signup / Login" button
65. Verify "Login to your account" is visible
71. Enter correct email address
77. Enter correct email address
83. Click on "Login" button
89. Verify logged in user