1. callTestCase(findTestCase("Login/L002_Login User with correct email and password"), ["userEmail":userEmail, "password":password], STOP_ON_FAILURE)
3. Launch browser
9. Navigate to url http://automationexercise.com
15. Verify that home page is visible successfully
19. verifyElementAttributeValue(findTestObject("Object Repository/Login/Menu_Home"), "style", "color: orange;", Short_Timeout)
23. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Object Repository/Login/img_Home"), OPTIONAL)
29. Click on "Signup / Login" button
35. Verify "Login to your account" is visible
41. Enter correct email address
47. Enter correct email address
53. Click on "Login" button
59. Verify logged in user
65. Click "Delete Account" button
71. Verify that "ACCOUNT DELETED!" is visible and click "Continue" button